{
  "q1" : {
    "question" : "Who was the founder of Springfield?",
    "A" : "Jebediah Springfield",
    "B" : "Shelbyville Manhattan",
    "C" : "Moe Syzslak",
    "D" : "Bob Terwilliger",
    "correctAnswer" : "A",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q2" : {
    "question" : "What is the name of the Simpsons' family dog?",
    "A" : "Snowball",
    "B" : "Poochie",
    "C" : "Santa's Little Helper",
    "D" : "Laddie",
    "correctAnswer" : "C",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q3" : {
    "question" : "What is Homer's primary job?",
    "A" : "Mr. Burn's Assistant",
    "B" : "Nuclear Safety Inspector",
    "C" : "Bartender",
    "D" : "Construction Worker",
    "correctAnswer" : "B",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q4" : {
    "question" : "Who are The Simpsons' neighbour?",
    "A" : "The Flanders",
    "B" : "The Lovejoys",
    "C" : "The Wiggums",
    "D" : "The Skinners",
    "correctAnswer" : "A",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q5" : {
    "question" : "How old is Lisa Simpson?",
    "A" : "Eleven",
    "B" : "Ten",
    "C" : "Nine",
    "D" : "Eight",
    "correctAnswer" : "D",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q6" : {
    "question" : "How old is Bart Simpson?",
    "A" : "Fourteen",
    "B" : "Twelve",
    "C" : "Ten",
    "D" : "Eight",
    "correctAnswer" : "C",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q7" : {
    "question" : "What Japanese dishwashing detergent mascot who looks like Homer?",
    "A" : "Mr. Plow",
    "B" : "Mr. Sideshow Mel",
    "C" : "Mr. Burns",
    "D" : "Mr. Sparkle",
    "correctAnswer" : "D",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q8" : {
    "question" : "What country is Groundskeeper Willie from?",
    "A" : "England",
    "B" : "Ireland",
    "C" : "Scotland",
    "D" : "Canada",
    "correctAnswer" : "C",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q9" : {
    "question" : "Who is the host of Channel 5 news?",
    "A" : "Robert Terwilliger",
    "B" : "Kent Brockman",
    "C" : "Herschel Krustofsky",
    "D" : "Troy McClure",
    "correctAnswer" : "B",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q10" : {
    "question" : "Who is the mayor of Springfield?",
    "A" : "Troy McClure",
    "B" : "Joe Quimby",
    "C" : "Tim Lovejoy",
    "D" : "Clancy Wiggum",
    "correctAnswer" : "B",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q11" : {
    "question" : "What kind of beer does Homer regularly drink?",
    "A" : "Alamo",
    "B" : "Budweiser",
    "C" : "Pawtucket Patriot",
    "D" : "Duff",
    "correctAnswer" : "D",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q12" : {
    "question" : "What instrument does Lisa play?",
    "A" : "Trumpet",
    "B" : "Saxophone",
    "C" : "Clarinet",
    "D" : "Oboe",
    "correctAnswer" : "B",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q13" : {
    "question" : "Who runs the Kwik-E-Mart",
    "A" : "Apu Nahasapeemapetilon",
    "B" : "Barney Gumble",
    "C" : "Cookie Kwan",
    "D" : "Gil Gunderson",
    "correctAnswer" : "A",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q14" : {
    "question" : "Which family member joined Mensa?",
    "A" : "Marge",
    "B" : "Bart",
    "C" : "Homer",
    "D" : "Lisa",
    "correctAnswer" : "D",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q15" : {
    "question" : "In most episodes, who is Mr. Burn's assistant?",
    "A" : "Carl Carlson",
    "B" : "Waylon Smithers",
    "C" : "Homer Simpson",
    "D" : "Lenny Leonard",
    "correctAnswer" : "B",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q16" : {
    "question" : "What is the name of Homer's father?",
    "A" : "Abe",
    "B" : "Jasper",
    "C" : "Monty",
    "D" : "Homer Sr.",
    "correctAnswer" : "A",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q17" : {
    "question" : "What is Bart doing during the opening title sequence of most episodes?",
    "A" : "Handling plutonium",
    "B" : "Writing on a chalkboard",
    "C" : "Riding a bike",
    "D" : "Parking in the driveway",
    "correctAnswer" : "B",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "q18" : {
    "question" : "What type of power plant does Mr. Burns own?",
    "A" : "Coal",
    "B" : "Hydro",
    "C" : "Gas",
    "D" : "Nuclear",
    "correctAnswer" : "D",
    "type" : "Character"
  },
  "general" : {
    "inputErrorMsg" : "Please enter a valid value per the instructions in the prompt.",
    "categories" : "Character",
    "questionTotal" : "18"
  }
}

